

# NIKHIL DUBEY

IT ENGINEER

#### CONTACT



+91 8962132378



20.nikhildubey@gmail.com



88, Rajaram Nagar, Dewas (M.P.) 455001



https://acronikhil.github.io/NikhilDubey/

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Java
- Spring Boot
- Angular
- React
- React Native
- MySQL
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Python
- Django
- C / C++
- Cybersecurity
- Video & Photo editing

#### LANGUAGE

**English** 

Hindi

Spanish

• • • • •

#### **INTEREST**



**Traveling & Riding** 



Learning New Techs

# 01

### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Inquisitive full-stack developer with 2 years professional and 3 years freelance experience in as full stack developer, using Angular, React, Spring-Boot, Django, Python, HTML, CSS, JS, MySQL, etc. Worked on 12+ personal projects and developed applications using React-Native and websites using tools such as WordPress and Wix. Looking forward to use my skills and upskill myself by working in challenging projects solving user problems.

# 02

## **EDUCATION**

## B. Tech. Information Technology

Acropolis Institute of Technology and Research, Indore (2018-2022)

- Technical graduation in Information Technology
- On campus technical training in Cloud computing (AWS)
- Project development using full-stack development and machine learning.

### **Higher Secondary Education**

The Everest English Higher Secondary School, Dewas (2018)

• Completed schooling in Physics, Chemistry and Mathematics subjects in English medium.

# 03

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Capgemini

February 2022 - Present

### Analyst / Software Developer

 2 years experience, trained and worked as Java Full-Stack using Angular, Micro-Services using Docker, Kubernetes and cloud using AWS.

#### SagurlT

February 2021 - April 2021

## **React Native Developer (Intern)**

Resolving bugs and developing application.

The Entrepreneur Network

February 2021 - June 2021

### Angular Developer and Tester (Intern)

 Making website using angular and testing the working of application.

# TOP PROJECTS (FOR MORE PROJECTS CLICK ME)

#### • CRIMNAL DETECTOR | 1 Month(s)

- In CIMINAL DETECTOR we upload a image and the app compares the image uploaded by each image in database if match is found then it shows data of criminal from database.
- FEM PLAYER | 1 Month(s)
  - FEM Player is a Music player which plays music according to users mood by reading facial expression. It is A Smart India Hackathon project.
- STUPRO | 2 Month(s)
  - It is a Webapp made for students and other people to help them at new place by giving them
  - o information about nearest, cheapest Hostels, Rooms, Flats, Laundry etc. Also provides a connection
  - between service provider and users, competitive analysis in business.